Hi.
This is Jeff;
Jeff Strongman.
So what happened
between you and your girl?
She wanted to get married and
I'm just not sure I'm ready.
It's the same reason
I lost Lyndsey.
It's like we were
dating the same woman.
I am gonna ask Lyndsey
to marry me.
Lyndsey MacElroy...
will you marry me?
Yes! I will marry you!
Everything you need to know
is right in here.
Somebody gave me
a billion dollar idea--
thought controlled computing.
We have so much work to do
and all I can think about
is you and me-- wow...
Gotta stop thinking about sex.
This is Walden Schmidt
saying--
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Pudding.
I think the computer
just read his thoughts!
It worked.
(screams happily)
(laughs) Yes!
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Someone's not wearing a bra.
♪ Men. ♪
This is great!
My best friend, my fiancée
and a great bottle
of French wine.
Uh, uh, technically
it's French Canadian.
Uh, it's called
"Two-buck Canuck,"
and, uh, it's not wine,
it's wine-ish.
Um, but it still gets
the panties on the floor,
if you know
what I'm talking about.
(laughter)
Maybe you should have
another glass, Lyndsey.
I'm good.
Hey, uh, how about you, Larry?
No, I'm not wearing panties.
All righty, so, uh,
guess we're done with this.
So...
how long of an engagement
are you guys planning?
Uh, two years? Five years?
I mean, you know, there's
no rush to start a family.
I mean, after all, uh,
Lyndsey's well beyond
her child-bearing age.
Well, we have talked about
adopting a baby from China.
Oh!
Course, then we'd
have to teach it English,
which seems like a lot of work.
Would you mind
getting desert, sweetie?
Sure.
Um, kidding.
Uh, this one's on you, sweetie.
(Alan & Larry laughing)
All right, but no funny business
while I'm gone.
I'll know, Jeff.
(laughs)
You haven't so far.
I've been banging this one
for months.
(Alan & Larry guffawing)
LYNDSEY: Oh...!
I love this guy!
She does too!
(laughing)
Isn't this fun?
(laughing):
Yeah. It's great.
Why the hell are you here?
Larry asked me to dinner.
What was I supposed to say?
That you couldn't come.
That you had to work.
That you're not really
Jeff Strongman
and your entire friendship
is a lie.
That I had to work--
that's a good one.
(sighs)
Alan, this wedding
is very important to me.
If you still have
any feelings for me at all,
you will let me have this day.
Fine.
I shan't go.
(sighs)
But good luck getting
the Chicken Dance
started without me.
Hey, Jeff, you want
a piece of Lyndsey's pie?
There's no way
I can eat it all myself.
I don't know.
Last time I had some,
there was a hair in it.
Jeff was actually just saying
that he's got to get going.
Mm.
Really? Oh.
Well, then I'll
make this quick.
I know we haven't known
each other for a long time,
but I feel like
we share a lot.
M-More than you know.
So I was wondering
if you'd do me the honor
of being my best man?
What?!
What do you say?
I... say...
...you've made me
the happiest
person in the world-- yes!
(laughing)
You sure? Don't you want to
take a moment to think about it?
What is there
to think about?
You know, you could
change my name from
"Jeff Strongman",
to "Jeff Best Man."
(both laughing)
That's the kind of stuff
I want in your toast!
And this is the
kind of stuff
you're gonna get
on the dance floor:
(singing "Chicken Dance" melody)
(both grunting in rhythm)
(both laughing)
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x16 ♪
How to Get Rid of Alan Harper
Original Air Date on March 6, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Oh. Oh. Wait.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Hey, good lookin'.
Whatcha got cookin'?
Pot brownies.
What the hell is that?
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
It's a new project
I'm working on.
It enables a computer
to read my mind
and then talk to you.
Why can't you just talk to me?
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Because, I...
and this... shut up.
Come on, try it.
I think it's big enough.
I think it'll fit.
The last time someone said that,
I ended up pregnant
with my first daughter.
Hey... I got good news.
I'm paid to pick up your crap,
not listen to it.
Guess who Larry asked
to be his best man?
One of his friends
who's actually real?
Jeff Strongman is like butter
on movie theater popcorn.
He may not be real,
but he's delicious  nonetheless.
Okay, so, let me
get this straight:
your alter ego,
Mm-hmm.
is going to be the best man
at the wedding of your lover...
and another guy?
When you put it like that,
it sounds like
a soap opera on Telemundo.
(doorbell rings)
(Spanish accent):
Señor Strongman, why do you
make love to
the woman of the man you love?
Lyndsey?
Are you insane?
Oh, si, Señor Strongman
es muy loco.
How could you say "yes",
to being Larry's best man?
I don't know. I got excited.
And you and I both know
when I get excited, I tend to...
react prematurely.
Why would you even want to go?
Are you kidding me?!
I mean, just 'cause
you're mad at me right now
doesn't mean I'm going to miss
the wedding of someone I love.
Aw... that's very sweet.
I was talking about Larry.
Oh!
Ow!
Ah! Dios mío!
Alan, I don't care
how you do it,
fake Jeff Strongman's death--
actually die.
You will not be at my wedding.
(door slams shut)
(scoffs, laughs)
She will be back here in three
seconds looking for make-up sex.
One...
Two...
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Three.
You're an idiot.
I'm, um, I'm sorry.
That was wrong.
Tú eres una idiota.
♪ Men. ♪
All right, Bill Gates...
Steve Wozniak...
and Mark Zuckerberg.
Ooh, that's a tough one.
Yeah.
I'd definitely kill
Mark Zuckerberg...
...bang Bill Gates,
marry Steve Wozniak.
What?! That's crazy.
I mean, yes,
you have to kill Zuckerberg.
But you gotta marry Bill.
I mean, I've seen it before,
he is gonna
take those glasses off
and shake is hair loose
and you're gonna be like,
"Where did this guy come from?"
I hear you, but I'm still
marrying Woz.
I'm a boob man.
Are you guys playing
"Bang, Marry, Kill" again?
'Cause if you are,
I've got one for you:
Angelina Jolie,
Mila Kunis and me.
I would kill you
by banging you to death
on our honeymoon.
Aw...
(laughs)
And then after the funeral,
Angelina Jolie.
I would love to bang Mila Kunis.
Not gonna happen, Barry.
All right. I'm out of here.
I thought we were
gonna grab some dinner.
I can't. I got a thing.
You got a thing. I got a thing.
We put our things together,
we have some fun.
Hey, every time
I say stuff like that,
I get pepper sprayed.
That was one time, Barry and
my mom still feels bad about it.
I'll make it up to you tomorrow,
I promise.
What's your mom up to
these days?
Shut up, Barry.
Better hope I don't
run into Mila Kunis.
(scoffs)
Yeah, like that's gonna happen.
♪ Men. ♪
(doorbell rings)
Hey! There's my best man!
Groom goes the dynamite.
(imitates explosion)
(laughing)
Come on in.
I've got some beer on ice
and sports on ice.
Oh, yeah! You're right!
Uh, tonight's the finals
of the pairs ice dancing.
(laughing)
You're hilarious.
Hey, you got to do
this gay character
in your best man toast.
Uh, about that,
you know I'm-I'm-I'm not sure
that I'm the right person
to be your best man.
I'll probably just end up
drinking too much
and getting yelled at
by the bride
and singing a tearful,
yet moving version of
"All by Myself."
At least, that's
what happened at my wedding.
Well, you're not getting
cold feet, are you, buddy?
Well, no, it's just
that it's your special day.
I mean, y-you sure that there
isn't somebody more deserving
to be your best man?
A-a-a brother?
A college roommate?
Someone who knows
your last name?
God, you're a riot.
There's nobody
I'd rather stand with
at that altar than you, Jeff.
(sighs) Why do you have to be
so darn sweet?
Plus, I'm counting on you
to help me out
with the most important part
of this wedding--
bachelor party.
Outfits.
I was thinking black tie.
Sure, black girls, Thai girls,
whatever you want.
Larry, where can I
put this poop?
Ooh!
And who do we have here?
This is my sister Gretchen.
She just moved here.
Gretchen,
this is Jeff Strongman.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, from what I hear,
I should call you
"Jeff Best Man."
(whispering):
Oh, my God, that's what I said.
Um, so, where's your dog?
In the garage
trying to wipe his ass.
Now, I couldn't find the trash.
It's out back.
I got it.
(laughs)
You can tell I love her,
'cause I take
a lot of crap from her.
Get it? Crap.
(laughing)
And he's Mom's favorite.
I hear you.
Luckily, my brother's dead.
Oh.
So...
uh... uh, you just moved here?
Yeah. My brother's
letting me crash here.
I told him it was just
for a couple days,
but, between you and me,
it's a pretty sweet deal.
Huh. I should try that.
Part of me thinks
I should just stay here
till he dies.
Why stop there?
Why not move in with
the next guy who buys the house?
Yeah.
So, uh, what do you do?
I'm a vet.
I moved out here
to run an animal shelter.
Oh... so that
tasteful sports bra
covers a tender heart?
Well, the puppies at the shelter
aren't the only ones
that need support.
Well, I'd uh, I'd love to meet
your furry little friend.
Oh.
I mean, I'm talking
about the dog.
Um...
Not that I don't
want to meet--
Never mind, uh...
(laughs)
So, you run a shelter?
Yeah. I've always had
a soft spot for strays
that no one else wanted
to take in.
(whimpers like a puppy)
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Ho, ho, ho-- somebody
is gettin' laid tonight.
Thank you.
No, not you.
I just found a late night
booty call on Craigslist.
Hello, BoobaFett420.
You know, Barry,
sometimes the picture
isn't who you get.
Oh, tell me about it.
I used your picture.
Where's Nicole?
Ugh. Nicole.
Yikes.
This is gonna be tough.
What happened?
She's dead.
What?
No, she just blew you off again.
I was just trying
to soften the blow.
The second time she canceled.
Something's going on.
Look, I'm sure there is
a perfectly reasonable
explanation.
She say anything?
Just that she would
call you later.
But on the plus side,
I'm available now.
Dave and Buster's, party of two.
We're not going
to Dave and Buster's.
We're gonna track down
my girlfriend.
Now shut up and get in the car.
Oh, my God,
you sound just like my dad.
♪ Men. ♪
This is impressive.
How'd you track her down
at the restaurant?
GPS? Triangulate
the cell phone signal?
No, she asked me to make
the reservations for her.
(sighs)
Look at her in there.
Happy as can be.
(feminine voice): I'll have an order of
seared Walden's Heart.
Hold the trust and honesty.
(chuckling):
Okay, okay, let me try one.
You know, honey,
I'm worried about Bobby.
His grades have really
been slipping.
Who are you doing?
That serious-looking couple
in the corner.
(feminine voice): Well, I'm worried
about the fact
that you always have
to drive the baby-sitter home.
I'm just doing Nicole.
Well, somebody's doing Nicole,
but it's clearly not you.
(sighs)
Why does this always
happen to me?
Boy meets girl, boy falls
in love with girl,
girl breaks boy's heart,
boy ends up in car with
socially awkward friend.
Come on, man.
You know chicks.
She's probably just
playing hard to get.
"You can't just show up
at my house like this, Barry."
"Where'd you get
those pictures, Barry?"
"Stop washing my car
in jean shorts, Barry."
D-Do you have to notify people
when you move
into a new neighborhood?
Oh... (scoffs)
Who's that guy?
A waiter?
Yeah. A waiter
who likes to hug.
Oh! Maybe it's Bobby,
the son of the serious couple.
Will you stop that?
Hey, don't yell at me.
I'm not the one cheating on you.
You know, new rule:
no more talking.
(feminine voice): You know, honey,
I'm worried about the way
the man in that car
is treating his friend.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
What you doing?
Filling out an application.
You're getting a job?
No, I'm getting
a medical marijuana card.
"What is
your medical condition?"
Stress.
Brought on...
by lack of marijuana.
Hey, can I...
can I run something by you?
I think Nicole's cheating on me.
Why do you think that?
I followed her
and I saw her with another guy.
That can mean a lot of things.
Well-well,
we were supposed to go out
and then she canceled
last minute
and then she lied to me
about where she was going.
Bitch be cheatin'.
Guess who's dating someone new.
His girlfriend.
Really? That sucks.
Her name is Gretchen,
and she's amazing.
Is this the beginning of the end
of the whole Jeff Strongman
thing?
Uh, au contraire, uh, she's
actually dating Jeff Strongman.
She's Larry's sister.
Uh, oh, and, uh, I'm still the
best man in Lyndsey's wedding.
Standard best man stuff:
Throw a bachelor party,
give a toast at the wedding,
assume a false identity
and bang both the bride
and the sister of the groom.
Wow. When you put it that way,
it sounds like a soap opera
on Telemundo.
That's what I said!
What does Lyndsey think
of all this?
I don't know.
Um, Alan hasn't told her
and Jeff Strongman
doesn't care.
How is it that Señor Strongman
has two girls and I have none?
Because you're not willing
to lie
and treat women like crap
so you can get laid.
You're a romantic.
You think every girl you meet
is your soul mate.
You're ready to move in
after the first date.
We have a term for guys like you
in the Lesbian community.
It's "lesbian."
♪ Men. ♪
Hey. How you doing?
Great.
I didn't sleep at all
last night.
I just kept thinking
about Nicole and that guy.
I found my first gray hair.
Not on my head.
Yeah. I didn't
sleep much, either.
I met up with BoobaFett420.
Turned out the "420" was
in reference to her weight.
NICOLE:
Hey.
Look who it is.
I'm really sorry
about last night,
but there's something
I want to talk to you about.
Is it your pants?
'Cause they're on fire.
'Cause you're a liar.
What?
We saw you at the restaurant
with a guy last night.
You followed me?
No, actually, we followed
a really handsome guy
who you had dinner with and
just happened to run into you.
I wanted to go
to Dave and Buster's.
All right.
Okay, I was waiting
for a better time
to tell you this, but the guy
I had dinner with last night
works for Google.
Oh... W... Get...
Barry, Google "betrayal" and...
Oh, actually, Bing "betrayal"
and let's see what comes up.
(Barry types rapidly)
Yep. Picture of Nicole.
I didn't really Google it.
That's my screen saver.
It's not what you think.
He offered me a job
in San Francisco.
They're working on
the same technology that we are,
and he said that I could pick
my own team and that's you guys.
Oh, my God.
NICOLE:
Yeah.
I've never been picked
for a team.
And you're gonna do this?
We are so close.
Well, they're a lot closer.
Wow. I mean, the chances of us
beating Google are one in a...
googol.
I bet we'll get
to make jokes like that
all the time at Google.
Who cares if they beat us?
We'll create something else.
All we have
to do is
believe in ourselves
and we can change the world.
Now, they're giving you an
opportunity to work for Google.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to be Google.
I have to take this. I'm sorry.
So you're just going
to San Francisco?
Where does that leave us?
Well, I mean, we were...
we were just having fun, right?
Yeah, fun. Okay.
Good. I'm just... I just...
(clears throat)
I'm glad you're not one
of those people who thinks
every person they meet
is their soul mate. Or...
that-that you would think
that we were moving in
with each other
just 'cause we had sex.
She's not a lesbian, dude.
I gotta call the guy back.
Go ahead.
Good luck in San Francisco.
Thanks.
All right.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I'm here for you.
Appreciate that.
You know, actually...
what she's offering
is a pretty good deal, so...
if you wanted to go with her...
Oh, thank God.
♪ Men. ♪
So tell me
about Gretchen.
Well, um, there
isn't much to tell.
I, um... I grew up
in Chicago,
I went to Northwestern,
became a veterinarian,
married the man of my dreams
but apparently he was dreaming
of banging
my best friend, so...
How 'bout you?
Uh, I haven't met
your best friend.
Is she hot?
You know I neuter dogs
for a living.
Are you threatening or offering?
(chuckles)
So-so, uh, what
brought you to L.A.?
Uh, just looking
for a fresh start.
You know? I mean, out here,
I can be whoever I want to be.
I can reinvent myself.
Mm. I thought about doing that.
But in the end, I can't be
anyone but Jeff Strongman.
Well, I wouldn't mind
a strong man in the end.
Ooh, dirty word play.
I'm vibrating.
I'm growing.
No, uh...
no, our-our table's ready.
Oh, great, great.
Uh, well,
let's take our wine
and have a seat.
Yeah, or, um,
you know, there's 20 minutes
left in happy hour.
I mean, we could just stay here
and fill up
on two-for-one appetizers
and half-off drinks.
Yes!
I mean, you know,
if that's what you want.
It's just... I hate
spending money unnecessarily.
Anything we don't finish
is going home with us.
I tell 'em
it's for the dogs, but...
woof.
Gretchen...
do you believe in
love at first sight?
♪ Men. ♪
(spits)
(coughs)
What the hell is "wine-ish"?
Hey.
How was the date?
Best... date... ever.
(chuckles)
We are perfect for each other.
It's like...
it's like God cloned me
and gave me boobs and a vagina.
Alan, can't you see
that this Jeff Strongman stuff
is only gonna
cause you problems?
Actually, I'm starting to think
Alan Harper is the problem.
I mean, Jeff Strongman
has a girlfriend, a best friend
and he's practically debt-free.
Practically?
He may have received
a free credit card offer
that was a little too good
to pass up.
Jeff Strongman has
a credit card?
And get this, Alan Harper got
100 bucks for referring Jeff.
Now I just need to figure out
a way to get rid of Alan Harper.
It's not as easy as you think!
(doorbell rings)
Barry.
I thought about what you said
and I decided...
I want to stay
and work with you.
I mean, I don't want to work
for Google.
I want to be Google.
Really?
Yeah.
I want to change the world.
(chuckles)
Hey.
We're gonna do
great things together.
Hell, yeah, we are.
All right.
So where do I sleep?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man